<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="16"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[VINEGAR






       FOOD






       RESTAURENT]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[SPECIALTY:






    Richly browned oxtail sections are simmered low and slow in a rich tomato sauce until the
    meat comes off the bones—this oxtail ragu is almost foolproof,” says Chef John. “The only

    way to screw up this incredibly succulent cut of beef is to not cook it long enough.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[GRILLED HOISIN BEEF



















     We love the sour tang of vinegar in salad dressings,


    marinades, and pickles. But lately, we’re getting our


    kicks from main dishes that offer a pop of vinegar. In



    dinner recipes like chicken adobo, hoisin beef, sweet


    and sour chicken, and slow cooker BBQ pulled pork,


       we just can’t get enough! Here are some of our


      favorite dinner recipes featuring sherry vinegar.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[SEA BAS A LA MICHELLE





            So here, we have grilled vinegar Fish with fried potato and roasted vegetables



                                                                               Also called Patagonian tooth

                                                                               fish, the Chilean sea bass

                                                                               is one of the most sought-

                                                                                                              d  The
                                                                               after fish in the world.
                                                                               once-obscure fish became a

                                                                               culinary celebrity during the

                                                                               1990s. Its flesh becomes oil-
                                                                               rich in frigid Antarctic waters


                                                                               and is hard to overcook.
                                                                               However, fish populations

                                                                               cannot keep up with the

                                                                               demand.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[GOOD FRICKIN, PAPRIKA CHICKEN














                                                                      “I really like oil and vinegar-based

                                                                     sauces on grilled meats,” says Chef

                                                                    John. “They work beautifully with the

                                                                   smoky, caramelized exterior. While this

                                                                     is a straightforward grilled chicken

                                                                   recipe, the vinaigrette at the end was a

                                                                     last-minute touch that worked out

                                                                                        nicely.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[DESSERT










                     The Best Chocolate Mousse


     The best chocolate mousse must be perfect. It should taste rich, indulgent and not too sweet, with
      a texture that is both light-and-airy and silky-and-smooth. After many attempts we nailed it and
      made a dessert that not only exceeded our standards, it's also quite easy to pull off. Close your
               eyes and take a bite — you'll be transported to a 4-star French restaurant.


       There’s a saying, “less is more” but when it comes to chocolate we

         say, “More is more”! Take these recipes, for example: chocolate

         layer cakes with candy bar topping, cocoa-dusted chocolate
            tarts, double-chocolate cookies — what’s not to love…….]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[CHOCOLATE-CANDY                                                    BAR LAYER




                                                     CAKE











     This cake will satisfy a serious chocolate craving (with its chocolate


     filling, frosting and candy bar topping) and makes for an easy cleanup,

     with just one bowl needed for the batter. Sweet!




     Instead of buying overpriced flowers and gifts, cook up a tasty treat for

     your special someone. Serve these as a special dessert, give them away

     to friends, or pack some in your little ones' lunchboxes.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[Instead of buying overpriced flowers and gifts, whip up a tasty treat for your special

    someone. Serve these for dessert, give them away to friends or pack some in your little

    ones' lunchboxes.


    For the Kids:


          Chocolate-Covered Banana Pops

          Crispy Rice Squares

          Triple Chocolate Cookies

          For the Kids at Heart:

          Chocolate-Covered Strawberries


          Chocolate-Hazelnut Smooches
          Cherry Almond Chocolate Clusters


          More Valentine’s Day Ideas:

          Aphrodisiacs: 5 Foods for Romance

          A Lighter Valentine's Day Menu

          Fall in Love With Chocolate]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[CHOCOLATE ANGEL FOOD CAKE




                           WITH STRAWBERRIES











      Although this angel food cake is loaded with rich chocolate


      flavor, it manages to be light as air. Top each slice with a

      spoonful of fresh strawberries tossed in a little bit of sugar.


      When preparing this indulgent chocolate mousse, Ellie


      Krieger uses silken tofu to create creamy texture for far less

      fat than regular cream. For restaurant-worthy presentation,


      spoon the mousse into elegant glasses and top with some

      whipped cream and dark chocolate shavings.










                                    If you're hoping to give a downright swoon worthy treat, Alton
                                    Brown’s Chocolate Fudge loaded with roasted nuts is the way to go.

                                    Pack it up in a decorative tin so your valentine can snack on fudge

                                    even after the glow of Valentine's Day is behind us.

                                    Your chocolaty treat doesn't need to be traditional. Bake a batch of

                                    quirky S’mores Brownies and your sweetie will surely become lovey-

                                    dovey. Either gift-wrap a few slices or hand over the whole tray. Hey,

                                    while you're at it, bake a batch for your office, your fam or your
                                    platonic "palatines." Everyone will appreciate these chocolaty squares

                                    of ooey-gooey goodness.]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[CHEF’S:

















     A chef is a trained professional cook and tradesman who is proficient in all
     aspects of food preparation, often focusing on a particular cuisine. The word


     "chef" is derived from the term chef de cuisine (French pronunciation: , the

     director or head of a kitchen. Chefs can receive formal training from an

     institution, as well as by apprenticing with an experienced chef.




     There are different terms that use the word chef in their titles, and deal with

     specific areas of food preparation. Examples include the sous-chef, who acts as

     the second-in-command in a kitchen, and the chef de parties, who handles a

     specific area of production. The kitchen brigade system is a hierarchy found in

     restaurants and hotels employing extensive staff, many of which use the word

     "chef" in their titles. Underneath the chefs are the kitchen assistants. A chef's

     standard uniform includes a hat (called a toque), neckerchief, double-breasted

     jacket, apron and sturdy shoes (that may include steel or plastic toe-caps).]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[CHEF DE CUISINE










       Main article: Chef de cuisine


       Other names include executive chef, chef manager, head chef, and master

       chef. This person is in charge of all activities related to the kitchen, which

       usually includes menu creation, management of kitchen staff, ordering and

       purchasing of inventory, controlling raw material costs and plating design.

       Chef de cuisine is the traditional French term from which the English word

       chef is derived.[2] Head chef is often used to designate someone with the

       same duties as an executive chef, but there is usually someone in charge of a

       head chef, possibly making the larger executive decisions such as direction of

       menu, final authority in staff management decisions, and so on.[3] This is

       often the case for executive chefs with multiple restaurants. Involved in

       checking the sensory evaluation of dishes after preparation and they are well

       aware of each sensory property of those specific dishes.



       In the UK, the title executive chef normally applies to hotels with multi

       outlets in the same hotel. Other establishments in the UK tend to use the

       title head chef.]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Education is available from many culinary institutions offering diploma, associate, and
      bachelor's degree programs in culinary arts. Depending on the level of education, this

      can take one to four years. An internship is often part of the curriculum. Regardless of

      the education received, most professional kitchens follow the apprenticeship system,
      and most new cooks will start at a lower-level 2nd or 1st cook position and work their

      way up.







                Like many skilled trades, chefs usually go through a formal apprenticeship which

                includes many years of on-the-job training. Culinary schools and restaurants offer

                these apprenticeships. To become an apprentice, one must be at least 18 years old and
                have a high school diploma or GED. Apprenticeships usually take 3 to 4 years to

                complete and combine classroom instruction with on-the-job training. The training

                period for a chef is generally four years as an apprentice. A newly qualified chef is
                advanced or more commonly a toquecommis-chef, consisting of first-year commis,

                second-year comis, and so on. The rate of pay is usually in accordance with the chefs.

                Like all other chefs except the executive-chef, trainees are placed in sections of the
                kitchen (e.g., the starter (appetizer) or entrée sections) under the guidance of a demi-

                chef de parties and are given relatively basic tasks. Ideally, over time, a commis will

                spend a certain period in each section of the kitchen to learn the basics. Unaided, a
                commis may work on the vegetable station of a kitchen.]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[The usual formal training period for a chef is two to four years in catering

     college. They often spend the summer in work placements. In some cases


     this is modified to 'day-release' courses; a chef will work full-time in a

     kitchen as an apprentice and then would have allocated days off to attend


     catering college. These courses can last between one and three years. In the

     UK, most Chefs are trained in the work place, with most doing a formal NVQ


     level 2 or 3 in the work place.]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[INTERIOR:





















     To offer a truly immersive dining experience, let your guests indulge more

     than just their taste buds the next time they visit  your  restaurant. Whip up
     a feast for the eyes with  restaurant  interior  design that wows your
     customers, while building brand recognition and loyalty.



     The best restaurant interior design creates an atmosphere that’s an extension
     of your brand and allows you to make a powerful first impression. In fact,
     color alone can influence up to 90% of a guest’s initial impression.]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[The beloved accent wall is a go-to restaurant decoration
        idea because it draws your guests’ eyes to a focal point. An

        accent wall also gives you the opportunity to show off
        your brand colors and personality, and reinforce the
        theme of your restaurant interior design. Try using
        textures, patterns, or even objects like the Taiwan Noodle

        House in Beijing, China.


















                                           Incorporating colors and styles that give a nod to your corner of
                                           the world is one of the most common restaurant decor ideas
                                           because it works wonders at setting a mood. This is an

                                           especially smart move if your restaurant is located in a tourist
                                           city or town, like Sisterhood, a restaurant with a beachy vibe
                                           based in Tasmania, Australia.]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Using typography as a restaurant decoration idea can help infuse your


     brand into the space. Try creating an accent wall with your restaurant’s
     name, like this typography mural at Malmö Restaurant in Valencia, Spain,

     which features the brand name alongside a few staple ingredients like

     eggplant, mushrooms, and nuts.


     Aside from being fun to use and reminiscent of worry-free childhood days,

     chalk is versatile and temporary, so you can use it in your restaurant to

     your heart’s content. Chalk works well for welcome signs, daily specials

     boards, and even your full menu, like this example from Broei Utrecht in

     the Netherlands.]]></page></pages></Search>